{
    "subject": "resource/John_H._Tilelli,_Jr.",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_H._Tilelli,_Jr.",
    "human_readable": "John H. Tilelli Jr. is the primary topic of this Wikipedia page.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789972901344299,
            "question": "Can you summarize the main points presented about John H. Tilelli Jr. on this Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9683149456977844,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of this Wikipedia page about John H. Tilelli Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9231511354446411,
            "question": "What can you learn about John H. Tilelli Jr. from this Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131312370300293,
            "question": "Does this Wikipedia page include any images or multimedia related to John H. Tilelli Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8938708901405334,
            "question": "Does this Wikipedia page provide information about John H. Tilelli Jr.'s early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803561329841614,
            "question": "Who is the primary topic of this Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.843396782875061,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements mentioned about John H. Tilelli Jr. on this page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082461953163147,
            "question": "What is John H. Tilelli Jr. known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7897394895553589,
            "question": "Are there any notable people mentioned in connection with John H. Tilelli Jr. on this page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5278294086456299,
            "question": "What are some key events or milestones in John H. Tilelli Jr.'s career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John H. Tilelli Jr. is the primary topic of this Wikipedia page.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1033_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable people mentioned in connection with John H. Tilelli Jr. on this page?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1033_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is John H. Tilelli Jr. known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1033_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements mentioned about John H. Tilelli Jr. on this page?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1033_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1033_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\nThe context provides information about John H. Tilelli Jr., including his military career, awards, and civilian life, strongly suggesting he is the primary topic of the provided Wikipedia excerpt.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is \"John H. Tilelli Jr.\" and it appears that I should be evaluating whether he is the primary topic of this Wikipedia page, based on the context provided.\n\nAfter reviewing the documents, I found a mention of John Harold Tilelli, Jr. in one of the files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1033/re-ranker-msmarco/28.txt), which suggests that he is indeed the primary topic of this Wikipedia page.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information discusses details about John Harold Tilelli, Jr., including his military career and post-military activities. Therefore, it supports the statement that \"John H. Tilelli Jr. is the primary topic of this Wikipedia page.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}